worldweb.com 2006-03-19

# WorldWeb.com Privacy Policy

WorldWeb.com understands the importance of protecting its users' privacy and thus is committed to complying with the following 10 privacy principles (as put forth in Canada's Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act). 

**1\. Accountability**  
WorldWeb.com has designated a Privacy Officer who is responsible for all matters regarding our privacy policy (please find contact information below). 

2\. Identifying Purposes   
The following outlines when and why we collect personal information:

BROWSING THE WEBSITE WorldWeb.com does not collect any Personally Identifiable Information when browsing our site. We may, however, collect information such as time of day, browser type and IP address. This information is used to make improvements to our site.

COOKIES WorldWeb.com collects information about your computer by assigning it a "cookie", a piece of information that is automatically stored by your browser. Cookies don't offer any personally identifiable information and can be turned off/on in your browser's preferences.

PURCHASING/RESERVING TRAVEL SERVICES When you reserve or purchase travel services through WorldWeb.com, we collect and provide information about you to the appropriate car rental agency, hotel or other involved third party. This is necessary so that you can complete your travel plans.

INTERNET POSTCARDS & SEND THIS SITE TO A FRIEND WorldWeb.com's Internet Postcards and Send This Site to a Friend features ask for the name and email address of both the sender and recipient. These features are provided to improve your travel-planning experience. WorldWeb.com does not share or distribute these names and email addresses in any other manner.

PERSONAL ITINERARY PLANNER WorldWeb.com' personal itinerary planner, called My TravelGuide, allows you to collect, store and print information found within the site. It functions using cookies (see above) and does not gather any personal information.

EMAIL FORMS WorldWeb.com readers are encouraged to contact the businesses listed within our directory using online forms. These forms ask for personal information i.e.) your name and email address. We require this information so that your email inquiry may be responded to. Any personal information gathered during these email inquiries is not shared with anyone other than the intended business.

OPT-IN MAILING LIST When filling out an email form (see above), WorldWeb.com asks if you would like to be included in our mailing list. This mailing list is periodically used to send you information about WorldWeb.com products and services. You may opt-out at anytime. 

3\. Consent  
WorldWeb.com assumes that you consent to the collection, distribution and retention of your personal information insofar that this information is used to fulfill your travel plans or to access your reservation history. Upon using WorldWeb.com services, you may withdraw your consent at anytime providing it doesn't conflict with legal or contractual restrictions. 

4\. Limiting Collection  
WorldWeb.com only collects information that is relevant to the services or products you are purchasing or using. We do not collect information indiscriminately. 

5\. Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention

Car and Hotel Reservations: WorldWeb.com stores personal information gathered during the travel reservation process in a secure database (please refer to the section titled Safeguards for information about our secure database). This information is kept so that you can access your reservation history. 

Memberships: WorldWeb.com safely stores records—online and in print format—of current and past WorldWeb.com advertisers/members. These records, which primarily contain information about businesses and little to no personal information, are accessed on a need-only basis and by qualified personnel. WorldWeb.com never shares this information with others. 

6\. Accuracy  
WorldWeb.com is committed to keeping your personal information up-to-date and accurate. If you are concerned in any way about the accuracy of your personal information stored at WorldWeb.com, we encourage you to contact us using the information provided below. 

7\. Safeguards  
Credit card information is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. This ensures that your browser scrambles data before you send it to us.

Any personal information gathered by WorldWeb.com is stored on our secure servers housed in a state-of-the-art data centre with 24-hour on-site security. This data centre also features intrusion detection systems, multiple Internet firewalls, bullet/fire/shatter proof glass and backup generator power. 

**8\. Openness**  
In addition to this online version of the WorldWeb.com Privacy Policy, WorldWeb.com will also make our privacy policy available in print format upon request. 

**9\. Individual Access**  
Upon request, WorldWeb.com will make available any personal information we have collected about you and disclose how it has been used (please refer to section titled Identifying Purposes for information about when and why WorldWeb.com collects personal information). 

**10\. Challenging Compliance**  
Any complaints about the WorldWeb.com Privacy Policy may be directed to us using the contact information below. All complaints will be taken seriously and dealt with in a timely manner. 

**Privacy Policy Contact Information**  
Tel: 403 777 9300   
Fax: 403 777 9304   
410, 1010 \- 1 Street S.W. Calgary, AB T2R 1K4 CANADA
